siteinspire.net 2019-12-01

# Privacy — siteInspire

We use cookies to identify your computer or device so we can deliver a better experience. If you access Siteinspire having signed in to your account, we record the IP address from which you are accessing the site. You can choose to disable cookies in your browser, but you will not be able to login or sign-up for an account.

If you choose to create an account on Siteinspire, we will collect personally identifiable information that you provide to us including your name and email address. If you choose to create a credit profile, we will collect additional details such as your address and website which will be used to be displayed on your publicly-accessible Directory profile. These data fields are voluntary, and your credit profiles can be edited and deleted here.

We do not knowingly contact or collect personal information from children under 13. If you believe we have inadvertently collected such information, please contact us so we can promptly obtain parental consent or remove the information.

We do not use or collect your precise geographic location. You may choose to voluntarily provide your address as part of a credit profile, which will be displayed publicly in the Directory.

You can choose to delete your account at any point by signing in and choosing the "Cancel Account" option. You can also [contact us by email](mailto:mail@siteinspire.com) to request to see or delete this information.

We remove personally identifiable information and other preferences associated with your account immediately after you delete your account. Any website submissions and credit profiles associated with your account will also be deleted immediately.

We do not share personally identifiable information including your name and email address with other companies for marketing purposes.

If you have any questions or concerns about our privacy policies, please contact us: [mail@siteinspire.com](mailto:mail@siteinspire.com).

In order to serve you, we may share your personal and anonymous information with other companies, including vendors and contractors. Their use of information is limited to these purposes, and subject to agreements that require them to keep the information confidential. Our vendors provide assurance that they take reasonable steps to safeguard the data they hold on our behalf, although data security cannot be guaranteed.

We use Google Analytics to help us understand how our services are used, but no personally identifiable data including your name or email address is shared. They use this data solely on our behalf. They do not share it except in aggregate form; no data is shared as to any individual user. [Click to see company privacy policies that govern their use of data](https://www.google.com/analytics/learn/privacy.html). You can review [Google's GDPR page here](https://privacy.google.com/businesses/compliance/).

In order to send the weekly newsletter, occasional news updates, and all transactional emails, we use a third-party service called SendGrid. Only your name and email address will be shared and will be used only for the purposes of sending emails. You can review [SendGrid's Privacy Policy here](https://sendgrid.com/policies/privacy/). You can choose to opt out of the weekly newsletter and news updates by unchecking the appropriate checkbox in your user profile. SendGrid's [GDPR page can be reviewed here](https://sendgrid.com/resource/general-data-protection-regulation/).

We share your name and email address with a third-party service called [Intercom](https://www.intercom.com/), who provide Customer Relationship Management tools that will be used by Siteinspire in the future. You can review their [Privacy Policy here](https://www.intercom.com/terms-and-policies#privacy). If you close your account or request to have your account closed, we will ensure the equivalent record on Intercom will also be removed. Intercom's [GDPR page can be reviewed here](https://docs.intercom.com/pricing-privacy-and-terms/data-protection/how-were-preparing-for-gdpr).

We take reasonable steps to secure your personally identifiable information against unauthorized access or disclosure. However, no security or encryption method can be guaranteed to protect information from hackers or human error.

We may make identifiable and anonymous information available to any successor or purchaser in a merger, acquisition, liquidation, dissolution or sale of assets. We will attempt to notify you of this, to the extent permitted by law to do so.

This privacy policy was last updated on April 25, 2018. Our privacy policy may change from time to time. If we make any material changes to our policies, we will place a prominent notice on our website. If the change materially affects registered users, we will send a notice to you by email.

Siteinspire is operated by Howells—Studio, a trading style of Kulor Ltd., whose registered address is 6a St Andrews Court, Thame, OX9 3WT, United Kingdom. We can be contacted at [mail@siteinspire.com](mailto:mail@siteinspire.com).
